{
    "id": "656577bca0d64b82a1e3e58bc60c73b9",
    "title": "Would Rather And Had Better",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I’d rather you ………………….. keep in touch with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fca27c31abbc4d47810d6ba057ba2a57"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ……………….. go through this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't to",
                "didn't have to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45e3722caa274e0fa0086e90bca8f324"
        },
        {
            "question": "You’d better ………………… a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "consult",
                "consulted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "866c651eff354698aa55e37a60fe946c"
        },
        {
            "question": "After the way he treated me, I wish I ..................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't marry",
                "hadn't married"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd4bc97ad68f4504b0b1137789759b66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’d rather …………….. on Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not to work",
                "not work"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4546e5996bf4027acebe8e23e2b3db8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ………………… your valuables in a locker.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "keep",
                "to keep"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "832fe9323be24838bb13ca735a1799d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had better …………………. for a drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not stop",
                "not to stop"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c6f30b5586c4fae89b79b47fa2de452"
        },
        {
            "question": "We could sack him right now, but ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I wouldn't rather",
                "I'd rather not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5308be7c2bd4403d92a8a20bb866d9b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ………………… there when they arrested him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "517dda58614e466e92dd7c4d2af4ac8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………… take this personally.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won't",
                "wouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48c05ab93af843ceb0cef1e5dbfa0435"
        }
    ]
}